(Leonard:)I don't know why I avoided the Harry Potter
books for so long. These are great.
(Leonard:)- I just started number six.
- That's a good one.
(Sheldon:)Dumbledore dies in that one.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I know, I didn't see it coming, either.
(Leonard:)Why would you say that?
You brought up a subject,
I contributed a fact on that subject.
(Sheldon:)It's called the art of conversation.
Okay, your turn.
(Leonard:)That was a huge spoiler.
(Sheldon:)Good.
(Leonard:)What is wrong with you?
If I did that, you'd bitch about it for weeks.
(Sheldon:)Really, Leonard?
Gonna have one of your hissy fits?
(Leonard:)Hissy fits? I have hissy fits?
(Sheldon:)Yes. And I have a theory why.
(Sheldon:)Because of your lactose intolerance,
you switched over to soy milk.
(Sheldon:)Soy contains estrogen-mimicking
compounds.
(Sheldon:)I think your morning Cocoa Puffs
are turning you into a hysterical woman.